A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Africa and Middle East Program, Regional Director, Office Files of Timothy Bork FA700
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Meeting Files, Organization Files A-B
  - Africa News Service (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 20)
  - African-Latin American Institute (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 21)
  - Africa Policy Information Center (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 22)
  - African Economic Research Consortium (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 23)
  - Africare (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 24)
  - Afropop Worldwide (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 25)
  - Akina Mama wa Afrika (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 26)
  - American University in Cairo (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 27)
  - AMIDEAST (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 28)
  - Ashoka (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 29)
  - Aspen Institute (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 30)
  - Association of Women in Development (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 31)
  - Association of African Universities (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 32)
  - BCIU (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 33)
  - Black Lawyers Association (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 34)
  - Bretton Woods (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 35)
  - Brookings (Box 5 (SK#38718), Folder 36)
- Organizations Files C-M
  - Cairo Institute for HR Studies (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 1)
  - CAPAS (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 2)
  - Carter Center (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Corporation (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 4)
  - Center for Advanced Social Science (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 5)
  - Center of Concern (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 6)
  - Children's Television Workshop (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 7)
  - Clarity Productions (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 8)
  - Clark-Atlanta University (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 9)
  - Codesria (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 10)
  - Constituency for Africa (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 11)
  - Corporate Council on Africa (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 12)
  - Council for the Advancement of Science (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 13)
  - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 14)
  - Dag Hammarskjold Foundation (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 15)
  - Development Resource Center (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 16)
  - Economic Research Forum for Arab Countries (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 17)
  - Emory University (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 18)
  - Environmental Quality International (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 19)
  - Foreign Policy Association (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 20)
  - Gremeen Bank (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 21)
  - The Unger Project (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 22)
  - IDEP (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 23)
  - IFESH (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 24)
  - State of Israel (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 25)
  - Israeli Center for International Cooperation (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 26)
  - Institute for Professional Legal Education and Training (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 27)
  - Institute of International Education (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 28)
  - Institute of War and Peace Studies (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 29)
  - Interaction (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 30)
  - International Development Law Institute (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 31)
  - International Human Rights Law Group (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 32)
  - International Peace Academy (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 33)
  - International Sociological Association (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 34)
  - Inter Press Service (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 35)
  - Kagisco Trust (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 36)
  - Kaunda Foundation (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 37)
  - Kennedy Center (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 38)
  - Legal Resources Center (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 39)
  - MERIP (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 40)
  - Museum of African Art (Box 6 (SK#38719), Folder 41)
- Subject Files, N-Z; A-J
  - National Center of Nonprofit Boards (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 1)
  - National Research Council (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 2)
  - Open University of Israel (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 3)
  - Overseas Development Council (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 4)
  - Oxfam (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 5)
  - PanAfrican News Agency (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 6)
  - Parliamentarians for Global Action (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 7)
  - Phelps Stokes Fund (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 8)
  - Rafi (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 9)
  - Safe (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 10)
  - Saferworld (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 11)
  - SAPES (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 12)
  - Social Science Research Council SSRC (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 13)
  - Southern Africa Affinity Group (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 14)
  - Sterling International Group (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 15)
  - Tel Aviv University (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 16)
  - TransAfrica Forum (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 17)
  - UN System-Wide Special Initiative on Agrica (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 18)
  - UNLA (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 19)
  - UNECA (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 20)
  - University of Cape Town Fund (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 21)
  - The Urban Foundation (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 22)
  - WARF - West Africa Rural Foundation (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 23)
  - Winrock (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 24)
  - World Peace Foundation (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 25)
  - World Vision (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 26)
  - York University (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 27)
  - Zayed Bin Sultan El Nahayan Foundation (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 28)
  - Arusha (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 29)
  - Clapp Proposal - SA (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 30)
  - Lincoln University (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 31)
  - Kaye Whiteman Proposal (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 32)
  - Shlih Booker (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 33)
  - Lynn Ellsworth - WARF (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 34)
  - Michael Ignatieff (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 35)
  - John Marcum (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 36)
  - FF Enquiry into Socially Transformative Theological Education in South Africa (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 37)
  - Jeswald Salacus (Box 7 (SK#38722), Folder 38)
- Program Reviews and Subject Files, 1986-1993
  - Program Budget 1993: Steve Riskin for Israel (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 1)
  - Joint Program Review, 1993 March 29 - April 8 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 2)
  - Joint Program Review - Guest/Guest Speakers (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 3)
  - Joint Program Review - Africa Regional Day, 1993 April 5 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 4)
  - Joint Program Review - Representatives/Assistant Representatives Schedules (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 5)
  - Joint Program Review - Joint Program Review (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 6)
  - Joint Program Review - JWT April '93 Program Review Africa Day, 1993 April (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 7)
  - Program Reviews USIAP/DCP 5/49 - 5/10/91 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 8)
  - Administrative Meeting, 1991 May 6 - 23 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 9)
  - Program Reviews, 1992 May 4 - 15 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 10)
  - Africa/Middle East Day, 1992 May 7 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 11)
  - African Diennial Budget Review - Dakar, 1990 February 18 - 25 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 12)
  - Regional Africa/Middle East Programs, 1990 October 29 - November 2 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 13)
  - FY 1990-91 Diennium (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 14)
  - Program Reviews, 1989 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 15)
  - FY 1989 USIAP Program Reviews (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 16)
  - Program Reviews, 1990 April 23 - May 4 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 17)
  - African Regional Program Review, 1989 February 4 - 10 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 18)
  - Program Reviews, 1986 October 10 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 19)
  - Publishing, 1991-1993 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 20)
  - Donor Group for African Publishing, 1991 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 21)
  - DCP Reserve Claims, 1993 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 22)
  - DCP Reserve Requests Africa FY 1993 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 23)
  - Reserve Requests FY 1993 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 24)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1992 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 25)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Health, 1990 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 26)
  - Service Award, 1991 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 27)
  - South Africa, 1991-1992 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 28)
  - South Africa AIDS, 1990 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 29)
  - ANC, 1991 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 30)
  - Archives South Africa Update (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 31)
  - South Africa Office, 1991-1993 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 32)
  - South Africa Constitution, 1993 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 33)
  - Sutton History Excerpts (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 34)
  - AAI Congressional Staff Seminar, 1989 July (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 35)
  - TransAfrica, 1992 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 36)
  - USAID, 1992 (Box 8 (SK#38720), Folder 37)
- Operations Files
  - Nairobi (Box 9 (SK#38721), Folder 1)
  - Harare (Box 9 (SK#38721), Folder 2)
  - Harare Office Opening (Box 9 (SK#38721), Folder 3)
  - Zimbabwe Closure (Box 9 (SK#38721), Folder 4)
  - Johannesburg (Box 9 (SK#38721), Folder 5)
  - Leslie Cerhart (Box 9 (SK#38721), Folder 6)
  - Windhoek (Box 9 (SK#38721), Folder 7)